http://www.keynshamswimmingclub.co.uk/team/reczzkscor/page/privacy

Sign in
HomeNewsSquads & timetableTraining scheduleKey PersonnelCoaches & CaptainsSquad SecretariesKASC CommitteeWelfare TeamCatchment Area MapDownloadsFundraisingEventsPrivacyLinks Keeping your Information Safe and Sound
At Keynsham Amateur Swimming Club we take your privacy seriously.
The notices on this page explain how we may use personal information we collect before, during and after your association with us. This applies to you if you have registered to become or are a member of our club, are a parent/guardian of a member of our club, or volunteer with us. We explain here how we comply with the law on data protection, what your rights are, and, for the purposes of data protection, we will be the controller of the personal information we hold.
Firstly, our privacy principles are summarised as follows:
Summary Privacy Notice written for adults
Summary Privacy Notice written for juniors
To see the full details of our approach to privacy, please select the document that best describes your relationship with us in the following table:
I am an adult member of KASC
I am the parent of a child who is a member of KASC
I am a junior member of KASC
I volunteer at KASC
Data Protection Policy
Anyone involved in helping to run Keynsham Amateur Swimming Club is expected to manage personal information in accordance with the club's data protection policy.
A summary of the club's data protection policy can be found here
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by TeamUnify but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by GoMotion but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
Privacy Statement
